Localization_Manager_Source
>Menu
GamePauseNote=Game Paused  
GameExitNote=Want to quit?
Menu=Menu  
Resume=Resume  
Exit=Save & Exit  
Start=Start  
Setting=Settings  
Back=Back  
BackToMainMenu=Back to Main Menu  
Confirm=Confirm  
Cancel=Cancel  
Yes=Yes  
No=No  
Restart=Restart  
Retry=Retry  
Next=Next
Apply=Apply  
Reset=Reset to Default  
AudioSettings  =Audio Settings  
VideoSettings=Video Settings  
ControlSettings=Control Settings  
GraphicsSettings=Graphics Settings  
LanguageSettings=Language Settings  
NotificationSettings=Notification Settings  
AccessibilitySettings=Accessibility Settings  
AccountSettings=Account Settings  
PrivacySettings=Privacy Settings  
NetworkSettings=Network Settings  
SaveSettings=Save Settings  
Chinese=简体中文
English=English  
Japanese=日本語
EffectVolume=Effect Volume
VoiceVolume=Voice Volume
Language=Language
ResetData=Reset Data
StartGame=Go!
ResetDataConform=Really reset game data?/You can't undo the deletion.
ResetDataComplete=Game reset successfully!
Author=Author
AuthorMessage=Author/lIdea/Gameplay/Code/Level/UI : Mahiro/lLocalization : FunForTime/lThanks for all the free art. /l/lContact/lQQ group: 496873889/lEmail: 3339462323@qq.com/lGive your suggestion or take part in game making yourself if you like the game. Join the group for updates. /lThis is our very first game, and we are happy to help anyone who is making their game. /l
GameMode=GameMode
GameModeExplanation=(Hard mode disables speed limit tip)
Normal=Normal
NormalExplanation=Full tips
Hard=Hard
HardExplanation=Hard mode disables speed limit tip
Real=Real
RealExplanation=To be continued
OK=OK
FullScreen=Full Screen
UnlockConform1=Use
UnlockXPnotEnough=No enough XP to unlock
UnlockConform2=to unlock
>Stops
Stop=Stop
Arr=Arr.
Dep=Dep.
BeiJing=BeiJing
Tokyo=Tokyo
Akihabara=Akihabara
Ueno=Ueno
Kanda=Kanda
Ebisu=Ebisu
Shinagawa=Shinagawa
Shinjuku=Shinjuku
NULL=NameUnset
TianQiao=TianQiao
QianMen=QianMen
ZhuShiKou=ZhuShiKou
DaShiLan=DaShiLan
YongDingMen=YongDingMen
Tutorial1=Tutorial1
Tutorial2=Tutorial2
OchaNoMizu=OchaNoMizu
>Messages
EB=Emergency Brake Pulled
RunWithDoorOpen=Run with doors open
RunThroughRedSignal=Run through red signal
SLE=Speed Limit Exceed
Deviation=Deviation:
Delay=Delay:
BonusScore=Bonus:
MissedStop=Missed Stop:
Passing=Passing 
Depart=Depart from 
PassengerBoarding=Passenger Boarding
StopAt=Stop at:
SpeedLimitNotConformed=Speed limit not conformed
ConformingSpeedLimit=Conforming Time：
ConformingText=Comforming
ConformedText=Comformed
HighScore=High Score:
Congratulations=Congratulations!
AccelerationExceed=G-Senser value too high
NoRing=No door bell rang before door closed
Score=score:
>Routes
TestRoute=Test
Route1=R1
Tutorial=Tutorial
BeiJingCentralAxisTourLine=BeiJing Central Axis Tour Line
Basics=Basics
Sign=Signs
Tutorial-Basics=Basics
Tutorial-Sign=Signs
>Tutorial
MoveAround=You can move the camera with 'A' and 'D' key. Use 'S' key to return to the default position. Try it now. 
SpeedUp=The power handle locates at the bottom-left corner of the screen. Press down arrow(↓) or left arrow(←) to apply power and speed up.
StationWarn=This Sign indicates a station ahead. The number below shows the distance between you and the station. The number in brackets is the maximum deviation allowed to stop at the station. Try to stop exactly when the distance become zero.
SpeedDown=You are close to the station. Press up arrow(↑) or right arrow(→) to apply brake and reduce speed when approaching. If you overrun the stop, press 'R' to reverse the direction. 
G-Sensor=There are four indicator locates at the top-right corner, which are speed meter, clock, passenger rate indicator, and acceleration sensor. You will be punished if the G value is too high since passengers might fall over.
StationTutorial=After you have stopped at the station, press 'O' to open the door and wait for passengers to get board. It is recommended to apply maximum brake when boarding to avoid unexpected rolling. 
StopScore=The more accurate in both distance and time you stop at a station, the higher score you get. Press 'T' to show the timetable of this run. /lSometimes you can see "Non-stop" sign in the timetable. /lIn that case, you are required to pass instead of stop at the station at specific time. 
DoorBell=When all the passengers are on board. Ring the bell using 'B' to alert passengers. Remember to ring the bell for at least 5 seconds before closing the doors. 
NextStop=Now try to move to the next station all by yourself. 
TerminalStop=This is the terminal station. Let all the passengers get off the train.
Terminus=Whenever you are closing doors in a station, ring the bell first, even at the terminus. Although passengers arrived at their terminus, you still have a way to go. Speed up again. 
TerminusSign=This sign means end of your trip, stop anyway before the distance come to zero. Cheers for having learnt the basics of operating a train. 
StartPanel=This is start panel, which provide info of current route. Pay extra attention to the equation. In this case, a yellow signal equals to a speed limit of 45 km/h. This information will only show once during the whole trip. 
YellowWarnSignal=Here comes the yellow signal. The tiny orange light at the top indicates that this is an "announcing signal", which does nothing but informs you an actual yellow signal ahead. As mentioned at the beginning, a yellow signal equals to a speed limit of 45km/h, so make sure you are traveling at speed no more than 45km/h when running through the yellow signal ahead. 
YellowSignal=You have just run through a yellow signal, and the speed limit now has reduced to 45km/h. Keep your speed below that. Red signal often comes after yellow signal, so be prepared to stop. 
RedSignal=There's a red signal. You should never run through a red signal in any case. /lNow wait until it turns green. Going through a green signal will cancel the speed limit of previous yellow signal. 
SpeedLimitWarn=Here is an announcing speed limit sign, the number in circle shows the upcoming speed limit in km/h. The yellow ring around it indicates that it is announcing instead of actual speed limit. /lYou should press 'C' to conform the upcoming speed limit. It is called "Pointing and calling" in rail procedures, which forces driver to pay attention and reduce the chance they miss it.  
SpeedLimit=You have just run through a speed limit, which features a red ring. The speed limit now is updated to 60km/h./lAs you might noticed, there are number in black boxes along the way. They are distance sign and are placed each 100m. They are used to tell your position when in emergency, but you are free to  ignore them now. 
CombinedLimit=When both signal and speed limit sign are used, you should always follow the minimum limit. In this case, a 30km/h speed limit sign and a 45km/h yellow signal is a 30km/h limit.
RailClimb=Terrain may goes up and down. Pay attention to your speed and apply power or brake when in need. 
